<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Hide on bush</title>
    <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Hide on bush</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Construct3小游戏项目</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/construct3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 22:30:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/construct3/</guid>
      <description>用Construct3做一个LOL走a练习小游戏 演示视频：Bilibili
背景 英雄联盟(League of Legends，简称LOL)，也叫撸啊撸，是当代最热门的Moba类游戏。据不完全统计，至2015年7月为止，超过1亿名玩家每个月至少玩一次《英雄联盟》，而每天都玩的玩家超过2700万，高峰时段有超过750万人同时在线。2015年7月，该公司估计全世界每个月有超过1亿5千万名的活跃玩家。LOL已经成为当今史诗级的一款游戏，深受全球玩家喜爱。每年拳头公司举办的英雄联盟全球总决赛，更是成为了一个重量级的电竞赛事，吸引了大量的英雄联盟爱好者前往线下观赛。在现今，不可否认的是，英雄联盟正逐渐成为像篮球、足球一样家喻户晓、老少皆宜的运动项目
ADC(Attack Damage Carry)，是这个游戏中很重要的一个位置，他们主要造成远程物理伤害，能够提供稳定和较高的每秒伤害，是游戏中破坏防御塔的主力和持续伤害输出的主要来源。而玩家需要熟练掌握ADC这个位置，一个很重要的基本功便是走a
”走A“通俗理解便是：边移动边攻击敌人。在LOL这个游戏中，游戏角色发出一个普通攻击(也叫平a)大致需要经过三个过程：攻击前摇，攻击发生，攻击后摇。攻击前摇便是在角色发出普通攻击之前的抬手动作，攻击后摇是角色在发出普通攻击之后的收手动作。攻击前摇和攻击后摇需要一定的施法时间，而这三个过程被成为普通攻击的一个周期。根据游戏机制，我们可以在攻击后摇的时候进行移动，因此我们可以利用这个时间间隔控制游戏角色进行走位，以拉开与敌人的距离或者躲避敌方角色的技能
伊泽瑞尔（Ezreal）是一个需要在当今版本非常强势的ADC英雄，它需要掌控者协调好平a和技能的衔接，因此我用Construct3做了一个EZ的走a练习小游戏，可以提供给广大ADC玩家用来训练自己的走a技巧
游戏玩法 游戏一开始的界面如下： 
玩家可以通过A+鼠标左键的方式对敌方英雄（劫）进行普通攻击，也可以通过Q键向鼠标方向施放技能，每个劫的血量为5,每个普通攻击可以给予劫1点伤害，每个技能可以给予劫2点伤害。劫的血量降到0以下后会被击杀，系统每3秒会在地图中随机产生一个劫，并劫会持续向着玩家（EZ）的方向靠近。玩家可以通过右击鼠标点击地板进行移动，但是在攻击的时候会停止移动。每击杀一个劫，记分板上会增加分数，看看你能拿到多少分数吧！
游戏制作 创建工程 首先进入以下网址：

然后点击New Project,会弹出来以下框框： 
然后我们点击Creat，便可以创建一个工程： 
创建背景图 我们需要创建一个类似召唤师峡谷中的地图，于是我们可以进入英雄联盟训练模式中截取下路兵线交汇处的地图： 
然后点击工程界面的空白处，会弹出： 
我们点击Tiled Background，发现指针变成了十字的模式，点击工程画布的空白处，会弹出： 
在这里我们可以选择背景的样式，我们选择上面工具栏的第二个按钮来导入我们先前截取得到的背景图，可以得到以下结果： 
然后就可以关闭这个窗口啦，因为背景图我们一般是不移动的，我们可以背景，选择把这个背景锁住： 
这样子我们的背景就已经创建完毕了
创建人物 与创建背景图一样，我们双击画布空白处（因为背景图已经锁定了，双击背景图也是可以的），弹出以下窗口： 
我们点击Sprite进行创建，同样会弹出一个空白的模版，与创建背景图相同，我们只需要把抠好的图导入变好啦
在这个游戏中需要的物体模型只有四个，分别是：
 EZ 劫 Q技能 平a  这些模型的图片都可以召唤师峡谷中通过截屏找到-
除了将这些模型进行导入之外，我们还需要设置模型的碰撞体积和重心点，系统会根据前者来判断是否会发生碰撞事件，后者决定该物体的Position
以EZ为例： 
我们点击左边工具拦的最后一个，然后会出现一个由多个小正方形连接而成的方框，我们调整这些小正方形的位置，使它们紧贴着EZ的身体，便可以将EZ的碰撞体积缩小到模型本身的身体范围
然后是重心点的位置，我们点击左边工具栏的倒数第二个： 
可以看到出现一个小棱形，我们把这个小棱形的位置放到人物的中心中会更加合理
以同样方法可以创建另外3个模型，方法很简单，难的只是找到好看的素材
给模型添加动作方式 不同的模型可能会有不同的运动方式，比如EZ的运动方式是点到点的，因为我们是用鼠标右键来控制他的移动；而Q技能的运动方式是直线的，因为我们不应该保证Q一定能命中
以EZ为例，我们点击EZ这个模型，然后在左侧的状态栏里找到Behaviours这一栏，然后在最后有一个Add/edit Behaviours的选项，我们点击它： 
然后点击Add new behaviour，弹出： 
滑倒Movement部分中，我们可以看到这里有很多的运动方式可以添加，对于这些运动方式的区别请到官网查询文档，在这里EZ需要的运动方式是Move To方式，我们点击它，发现就会加入到已有的behaviours里面了
当然这里只是添加了一种移动的方式，如何控制它是在后面的事件触发行为中设置
以同样方式可以给另外3个对象也添加对应的移动方式</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install hugo on ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/hugo_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 22:30:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/hugo_setup/</guid>
      <description>Use Hugo on Ubuntu 关键一步 在~/.bashrc上加上：
export PATH=$PATH:/usr/local/bin/hugo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ML-Perceptron Model</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 22:30:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/ml/</guid>
      <description>机器学习之朴素贝叶斯法 简介 朴素贝叶斯法是一种分类方法，主要是从训练集中根据统计规律学得分类方法。对于给定的输入x，利用贝叶斯定理求出后验概率最高的类别y
基本方法和推导  Input:$x = (x^{(1)}, x^{(2)}, ..., x^{n})$，为输入变量的特征向量 Output:类别$y\in {c_1, c_2, ..., c_k}$  定义$X$为输入空间上的随机变量，$Y$是输出空间中的随机变量，我们要求的便是$max_{k}(p(Y = c_k|X=x))$，具体的方法是求出每一个$P_k(Y=c_k|X=x)$，然后选择概率最大的那个分类。
这个概率是后验概率，没办法直接通过统计数据得来（关于先验概率和后验概率），所以需要利用到贝叶斯定理： \(P(Y=c_k|X=x) = \frac{P(Y=c, X=x)}{P(X=x)} = \\\frac{P(X=x|Y=c_k)P(Y=c_k))}{\sum_kP(X=x|Y=c_k)P(Y=c_k)} \tag{1}\) 这里为了降低计算的复杂度做了一个合理的假设：输入空间中的特征都是不相关的，则： \(P(X=x|Y=c_k) = P(X^{(1)} = x^{(1)}, X^{(2)} \\= x^{(2)}, ..., X^{(n)} = x^{(n)}|Y=c_k) \\= \Pi_{j=1}^nP(X^{(j)}=x^{(k)}|Y=c_k) \tag{2}\) 这也是为什么叫“朴素贝叶斯法”（naive bayes），是通过合理性假设简化了运算的缘故。 则将（2）式代入到（1）式可以得到： \(P(Y=c_k|X=x) \\= \frac{P(Y=c_k)\Pi_{j}P(X^{(j)} \\= x^{(j)}|Y=c_k)}{\sum_kP(Y=c_k)\Pi_{j}P(X^{(j)} = x^{(j)}|Y=c_k)} \tag{3}\) 这里令$P^{&#39;}_k = P(Y=ck)\Pi{j}P(X^{(j)} = x^{(j)}|Y=c_k)$，则（3）式可变为： \(P(Y=c_k|X=x) = \frac{P^{&#39;}_k}{\sum_kP^{&#39;}_k}\tag{4}\) 很明（4）分母对于一个训练集来说是一个定植，那么我们的朴素贝叶斯分类器便可以表示为： \(y = argmaxP^{&#39;}_k \\= argmaxP(Y=c_k)\Pi_{j}P(X^{(j)} = x^{(j)}|Y=c_k)\tag{5}\)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>用电路做加法</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/circuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 22:30:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/circuit/</guid>
      <description>使用EveryCircuit来做电路实验 任务0：验证非门 电路图如下：

输入为1：

输入为0：

真值表为：
   INPUT OUTPUT     0 1   1 0    任务1：建立一个简单的电路 电路图如下：

测试结果如下：
   
真值表如下：
   In A In B OUTPUT     0 0 0   0 1 0   1 0 0   1 1 1    任务2：验证电路等价 电路图：</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Grammer</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 22:20:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/markdown/</guid>
      <description>Markdown Hello there! I’m Markdown, the Markdown editor for OS X.
Let me introduce myself.
Markdown and I Markdown is created as a simple-to-use editor for Markdown documents. I render your Markdown contents real-time into HTML, and display them in a preview panel.
I support all the original Markdown syntaxes. But I can do so much more! Various popular but non-standard syntaxes can be turned on/off from the Markdown preference pane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: Quasimodo</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work. The little chapel situated opposite the marble table was selected for the scene of the grinning match. A pane broken in the pretty rose window above the door, left free a circle of stone through which it was agreed that the competitors should thrust their heads. In order to reach it, it was only necessary to mount upon a couple of hogsheads, which had been produced from I know not where, and perched one upon the other, after a fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hide-on-bush2.gitee.io/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
